[Music]
Sonic this isn't good for you you really
need to go to sleep if you don't how can
you expect to wake up bright and early
for Papa John's tomorrow
okay I won't go to sleep I cannot
I refuse to not until Bartleby sings me
my good night song
you know the song that Bartleby sang to
me every night for the past five years
before bed
yes our mother my bro is not going to
sleep until he gets his good night song
from his lover
besides you didn't even bother buying
garlic butter sauce you Cheapskate Manic
the garlic but a sauce is free with
every Pizza what are you talking about
shut up
look son I can try and give him a call
but you know he won't answer explain
fool
Barca B is over in China taking part in
the National Chinese karate
championships
apparently he won in 12 seconds so he's
going to be giving interviews to Chinese
people in [__]
but he's wearing a yellow belt in this
picture
does that mean Bartleby didn't make it
all the way to becoming a black belt
karate master
that's not the world it's submitting
rather
that's the legendary golden devil
is
[Music]
not fair why would he make me a promise
that he couldn't keep doesn't he love me
he said that he would sing it to me
every night
I thought I was important to him how
could he break that promise to me
yes how could I ever indeed
now what with all the sad faces in here
today should be a cause for celebration
wouldn't you say
look I brought orange chicken for
everybody script from China itself
art lebby you're here but I thought you
were in Japan
I was but I used a helicopter to fly
back home after rabbit Jackie Chan in
the finals at the karate tournament
you didn't think for a moment that I
would forget to sing you your good night
song did you
I've been singing it for you every night
for the past five years don't you
remember
now scoosh on over those cheeks [__]
give daddy a place to sit
[Music]
ES
Millions
[Music]
can make you cry cry
now lie down and get some sweeper if you
need me I'll be downstairs eating a bowl
of macaroni salad
oh
wait are you sure we should be
contacting the Sonic Underground in the
open what if your rival L catches wind
of this rank [__]
the time for talking is over my shinig
on me now is the time for action
if we don't inform the Sonic Underground
of the anti-sonic underground fan club
now the entire world no worse than that
Sonic Underground as we know it will be
destroyed more than Elle's ass when I
get my hands on him
okay the light I trust you I know you
trust me fool that's why you're
comfortable enough to walk around with
your nipples out
Your Light Yagami I saw you in the news
you're supposed to be the number one
Japanese high school student why are you
here at my house at night in the middle
of America
because the time has come Sonic the
Hedgehog get all of your friends on the
phone and tell them to meet up here
if you don't I'm afraid we are all in
Mortal Danger
and that's why we need to stop the
anti-sonic underground does anybody have
any questions
yes bartlebby
so you're saying there is this top
secret organization calling themselves
the anti-sonic underground and they want
us all dead
yet you basically just explained in four
seconds what took me six hours to
explain
should you teach instead do you want me
to wipe your ass too
do you happen to know who these evil
boys are
for that question I have good news and I
have bad news which do you want to hear
first
I've been having a swell day so let's
keep that going good news first please
okay the good news is that one of them
is already dead I killed him with the
Death Note the bad news is I don't know
the identities of the rest
although I came up with an ingenious
plan
this is Jimmy a boy who recently joined
their ranks if we can capture him he
can't tell me the names of the boys he
is working with and I can eliminate them
in one Fell Swoop with my mighty Death
Note
today I recognize him
me and maybe saw him getting an
interview on the Dr Phil show I always
knew he was up to something no good
perfect bartlebby do you have any clues
as to where he might be at this current
time
you make me laugh like you got me I can
lead you to him right now the Tomato I
threw at him on the Dr Phil show had a
tracking beacon on it let's go snagging
you guys and notice how I only said guys
because everyone knows girls can't do
[__]
Sonic I have a special job for you while
we capture Jimmy
for me your job is to go recruit to
special someone for our cause I already
have his address so I will send it to
you on your Android phone his help is
crucial to the success of the operation
are you certain he's around here
bartelby we've been searching for five
hours
a beach the tracking Beacon I placed on
him cannot lie he's here somewhere
hiding and waiting keep your eyes open
look over there can you see it there's
something over there giving off magical
properties
Light Yagami are you okay
how curious this thing it's not just
some strange phenomenon it's a portal
like obsidian from Minecraft
a portal to Starry Godmother's domain
Jimmy must have fled through here
did he know we were coming after him it
doesn't matter we're going through
everyone hold on to your butts
[Music]
good everyone made it here safely we
should be clear I don't think anybody
saw us
hey what the hell happened to us where
did we get these Halloween costumes all
of a sudden what the hell is going on
light
the scary Godmother's domain is one of
Perpetual Halloween and spectacular
Spooks it's only natural that we would
be affected during the crossover into
this place thankfully this will work in
our favor we can go undercover more
easily like this
now you all remember the plan don't you
hold on light what about you you are not
wearing a Halloween costume
the green man has a point shouldn't you
be dressed up as a spooky monster as
well oh yes I understand what you mean
however
deep down in the darkest reaches of my
heart I already am a terrible monster
and this monster will someday have to be
punished for his crimes
hopefully byel pooping on me with his
butt haha just kidding like I would ever
lose to that [__] this is my game Andel
is my little pun to play with however I
like someday I'll figure out your real
name L and when I do you're dead
sir bartelby do you have a reading on
Jimmy's whereabouts it would seem like I
do judging my tracking Beacon he appears
to be just via 40 meter
that would Place him right at that
strange looking Mansion Over Yonder
well what are we waiting for let's make
like a black kid's dad and move out
you made it all the way to the roof
did I say you could talk [__]
you were right Jimmy throwing toilet
paper on people's houses is so much
funner than throwing eggs I know right
it symbolizes that these people are
pieces of [__] and not in the sexy kind
of way
hey guys the scary Godmother's front
door has glass panels do you dare me to
see if I can break it just by farting on
it
no
okay I'm going to do it anyway
Timmy stop this isn't funny anymore but
that is going to spank me if he finds
out about this and not in the sexy kind
of way
let's just go trick or treating and get
Reese's Peanut Butter Cups
look what I can do
foreign
you used to be so cool to be around but
since you started hanging around with
that group of guys calling themselves
the anti-sonic underground to flow all
you want to do is put me in pranks and
kill people
but didn't they always do that
Hannah would you be a deer and go make
sure that sound coming from outside
isn't the police
Hannah aren't you forgetting something
that's better that's much better
that's it who's out there pooping on my
scary Godmother's doorstep get out of
here
oh man Jimmy I should have known it was
you
pee sash it let's see if you can keep
talking like that by the time I get up
there to beat your ass
Daryl hand me my bullet case we're
taking down Hannah and all of her little
friends
this is not good there's going to be a
fire fight soon it's in our best
interest to capture Jimmy before any
harm falls upon him yeah there's no
point in interrogating him if he's dead
as a [__]
um which one is Jimmy again
take a wild guess
look at him over there dressed has the
devil releasing his dark desires of sin
out into the world God created
despicable
that ain't the only thing he's releasing
you go sneak around time and cut off his
Escape if he tries to leave
are you sure about that he's got a
[__] gun
and I've got bits and pieces of a
trillion dollar bill stuck in between my
booty cheeks because I pooped and wiped
my ass this morning your feelings don't
matter to me
what do we do
why are you asking me I'm just a sexy
rich boy I thought you were the ones
with a plan
thank you
stop right there Jimmy you're coming
with us
[__] it's the Sonic Underground the
other members of The anti-sonic
Underground club were right
they said you would come for me
yet well here we are now tell us names
of who you are working for before I pop
the cap up in that cute little tight
butt
I'm not telling you [__] white boy
you'll have to pound it right out on my
ass
so if you know what's good for you get
out of my neighborhood this is our turf
wait a minute that costume those horns
and the way those tights hunt your fat
butt
I see now you might act like you're with
the Sonic Underground but manic you are
not
you are like me a creature of a night
and worshiper of the Antichrist
join me that your friends and become a
member of the anti-sonic underground fan
club
we are living proof that Sonic
Underground sucks balls
no Jimmy all you are is living proof
that Sonic Underground haters belong in
the fires of hell
Perfect Right Where I Belong
it's a shame you don't want to join us
Manic the anti-sonic underground fan
club has been running low on funds
lately and you would have made a fine
prostitute with that fat butt
foreign
look out I think there's a white guy
hiding in the bushes trying to kill you
oh [__] not again
you brought your friends here to kill me
dammit my life's been living hell ever
since I went on that stupid Dr Phil show
I'm out see you later [__]
cover my thick ass my creatures of the
night I'm heading inside to kill Hannah
make sure they don't get to me before I
complete my mission of Darkness
did you hear that Jimmy's gone a whole
ass we can't let him out of our sights
or it's over
don't worry homeboy I got this
Ohana YooHoo where are you my sweet
sister it's time to play
hey nobody is allowed to come inside the
scary Godmother's house unless they are
invited and I can't think wholeheartedly
that you weren't so leave before I
grabbed you by the ass cheeks and drag
you out myself
please I don't do this I'll give you
anything I'll even let your stinky ass
crap
I'll [__] rape you [__]
you you're still here you're foolish for
coming after me boy taste my Steel
put the firearm down Jimmy nobody has to
die here today
we only came here to talk with you
flies I know you're here because I
joined the new boys
you want to kill me just like you want
to do to them
he's not listening to reason
what do we do now
Sony what the heck are you doing here I
thought you stayed back because you're a
weak ass [__]
I couldn't just sit by and do nothing so
I followed you guys but now I'm scared
maybe a girl's Place really is the
kitchen instead
hide and seek as a child's game don't
you think come out and fight me like a
man
I've got you now
you are not going anywhere
hurry-knuckles tie him up while I got
this little [__]
who are you people where are you taking
my brother
that's none of your concern go home
little girl before you get caught up in
our Miss yeah [__] I'll cast a spell on
your ass
good Brave to stand before me boy
especially after I ripped all of your
friend's heads clean off
how old did you say you were again
that's right it was nine
I will grant you a swift death by the
way I like your costume you look like a
bag of barbecue chips my [__] really
loves to snack on those things
that seems to be all of them
I know who I have a
how long is that lasted a kid now going
to take doesn't he know we are under a
strict deadline
I'm right here you seriously all out
here doubting me Knuckles the cool
echidna the [__] wrong with you all
when I say I'm gonna do something I go
out and do it
okay
Jimmy are you wearing pants underneath
your devil costume
of course I am why give them to me
people who don't like Sonic Underground
don't deserve to wear pants
I'll wear them for now if you decide to
change your ways someday you can have
them back oh and do mind the poop stains
here's the deal kid I want you to tell
me the names of the boys you are working
for if you can't do that I just might
leave your name out of the death note
you can walk away and continue living
your pathetic life how does that sound
that's okay you don't need to answer
your silence tells me all I need to know
Jimmy you're scared scared of me because
I am Kira
and hear this I am not only justice but
also God of a new world
do you really expect me to believe that
you can't kill me just by writing my
name in that notebook of yours
that's a pile up bologna it's not real
if you want proof I will grant you what
which you seek
take hold of the slip of paper in your
hands
if you are within possession of a piece
of the Death Note you will be able to
see
with your very own Naked Eyes a
Shinigami a god of death like no other
oh my God it's a shiny yummy they really
do exist
I can't see it
I'll tell you everything so please
please spare me
so I presume we are done here very good
alcohol my [__] on my 64 trillion gold
carrot cell phone to inform him that we
captured the target
thank you [__] are you there pick up
the phone for your daddy boy hello
this is Sonic the Hedgehog brother of
Manic the Hedgehog
who do I have the honor of speaking with
[__] it's your sweaty daddy we
completed our mission where are you
right now
I'm still in Domino City looking for
eugeo I think I see him
but he seems to be more dressed up to go
to a gay strip club than to play card
games
that's probably him I went to a business
meeting at Kaiba Corp once and eugeo was
there getting his fat ass slapped by
Kaiba it was a little too [__] gay so
owlette
okay I'll get back to you later when I
obtain the target
now to go get eugeo's help to defeat a
new boys if what light said is true his
help will be vital towards our victory
in this war
Cracker Jacks a duel is already underway
he's fighting his arch nemesis Seto
Kaiba
it's finally time you admit defeat
little Yuki I've gone through a rigorous
training regimen that involves making my
little brother dress up to look like you
so I can illegally grope his ass
your odds of winning are through here
today
first you've threatened to jump off the
roof of a building that the Duelist
Kingdom and now this kaibot you're a
sick man and sick men like you deserve
to be punished in the ways of duel
monsters
I wonder can you you're all out of cards
Yuki you have no cards left on your side
of the field and only one card in your
hand
me however I have three blue eyes white
dragons on my side of the field five
whole cards in my hand and Fort rap
cards face down
why don't you spare us both the time and
admit defeat
[__] he's tight and backed into a corner
Pharaoh looks like I'm gonna need your
help in this one
it looks like you're getting your speed
once again my partner what do you say
about going back home to your grandpa's
house after this duel so we can spruce
up that shitty deck of yours you're
playing like a little baby [__] who
needs his mommy to wipe him and change
his stinky diaper
shut up I don't need to bother with the
crack when I've got you to win all my
tools for me
what's gotten into you lately you've
changed where did your heart of a
duelist go you started wearing tight
pants and sleeveless shirts are you
doing this just so you can check out my
hot body
so what if I am I'm the one in control
not be Pharaoh now get out there and win
my match
I will but I won't like it
[Music]
at last he's finally here the Pharaoh my
want Revival
that's right this match is over
what you only have one card left there's
no way you can defeat me with just one
measly card
think again
is Monster aboard
I can bring back any number of monsters
from the graveyard that were destroyed
during this duel
monster reborn only lets you bring back
one card
well I'm not doing that
the monsters I choose are the Egyptian
god cards Obelisk the Tormentor Fly For
the Sky Dragon and the wind's Dragon of
rock I also summoned the almighty Dark
Magician and Celtic Guardian from my
hand
wait how do you have more cards in your
Yuki are you cheating
are you ready k-bar the real fight
starts now it's time to do
amazing so this is the power of the king
of games the power I must overcome
now travel in fear my Egyptian god cards
Earth shaking power [__] fly for the
sky dragon attack and take out the rest
of his life points
[__]
never beat me I'm the king of games and
do you want the penalty we usually use
for our matches where loser must suck on
the Winner's big juicy balls how about
we change things up for a change drop
your pants and turn that big butt around
let me get a big smelly whiff of those
butt cheeks
how did you beat me I thought all of
your best cards were gone
wait why is 30 of my cards missing from
my deck
so what did you do my eternal rival
return my cards at once before I get
very angry with you
it wasn't me Pharaoh it was one of your
loser friends they threw away your carts
no you lie it's true Yuki I saw the
whole thing it happened yesterday
[Music]
I was spying on you through your window
for reasons I will not discuss
I saw Kristen came to pay you a visit
and what he did still sickens me to my
stomach
hey key
borrow your cards for a second let me
borrow your [__] cards
sure Tristan but give them back to me
when you're done I have a shop
tournament this afternoon
you used our very own bond of friendship
against me did you really throw away my
cards
but why
you will never understand your key all I
ever wanted was to be noticed by you to
be accepted and praised by you
but the only person you care about is
said alkaiba I was illness of that
because I'm bad at dueling
I thought that if I threw away your
cards that I could finally beat you in a
duel and show no work to you and be
loved
Tristan the respect Kevin and I share
for each other will never be obtained by
you
you always be a loser with no life
let me show you fools that no matter
what disadvantages bring to the table
I'll always be the chain of kids
go dark magician use your dark magic to
blow them out of my sight
you made a grave mistake choosing
Tristan to help you but he didn't he is
the only one in my friend group that
doesn't even know how to play duel
monsters
now my dark magician
it's time to attack and win this duel
please I beg of you don't do it I'm so
sorry for what I did
no Tristan you stole my precious courts
and threw them in the garbage can a mind
crushes to good for some [__] like you
and so is the sweet mercy of death you
deserve a stronger punishment
please I can't change just give me
another chance shut up nobody here likes
you and it's for that reason I must send
you to the shadow realm for all eternity
did I ever mention
when you get sent to the shadow Realm
you lose all of your clothes because you
become my [__] [__]
[Music]
Yukio I need to talk to you
Sonic Hedgehog your bottle Beast [__]
what are you doing here in Domino City
I came for your help there is this evil
group causing trouble they're calling
themselves Sonic I already know
you do yes I've seen all that I needed
to see to know that it is time for Sonic
Underground fans like me and said okay
but to take a stand but we aren't the
only ones that are rising so are people
who hit Sonic Underground a war is upon
us
just give a word Sonic and we'll be
there
hello who could this be is it possibly
my [__] who's ready to tell his daddy
some good news
[__] hurry up and speak you're wasting
my minutes
it's me Bartleby mission complete
a very good job eight meet back up at
headquarters and we'll continue the job
from there in just a few short hours
this battle against the anti-sonic
underground fan club will be over and
victory will be ours
night we are ready to return home
great
so you're gonna tell us those names now
or what you dinky little devil man
fine you win I'll tell you but only a
few promise not to kill me
I have a math test tomorrow and if I
don't get at least to be my dad will
spank me
hold that thought I gotta go over there
to drop a deuce
[Music]
don't think I don't see you over there
do you nasty little creep
what you just gonna stand there and
watch you [__] gay [__] why don't
you come rub your face in my poopy butt
ah
what's going on here I demand that you
let me go at once do you have any clue
who the hell I am we know exactly who
you were hero
Kira hold on that handsome sultry voice
damn it l when my father hears about
this you're finished
take him away
no don't Bartleby don't let them take me
I don't want to go
I wonder what staking light so long
yeah since when does it take seven hours
just to poop
if I better guess the anti-sonic
underground fan club have decided to
make their first move it's nothing out
like you got me first despite not being
an underground cast member how clever
you don't mean
but I do we have to come to terms that
light you got me from the hit TV series
Death Note is no longer with us
hello
yes this is Bartle Beast [__]
hey Sonic what's up
Rooney doodle my arch nemesis how did
you get this number I thought you were
in jail for the kidnapping of Tyler Ross
I wasn't now I got some demands so
listen up
demands you I don't even listen to the
woman's because I'm sexist you dumb
idiot
well you are going to want to listen to
these ones because if you don't
well let's just say your body light is
gonna have a really bad time if you're
scooping what I'm pooping
how could I have been such a fool of
course Rooney doodle my arrival
Doodlebop is with the Enemy
hurry Beach put it on speakerphone
like hell turn that [__] off before I
blow lights goddamn brains out
hurry Beach take it off speakerphone
now I'm going to make this plane end
simple no tricks tomorrow when the clock
strikes noon it's going down
bring your friends to the Big Lots
parking lot situated down the street
between the RBS and Subway
that is where we will settle this matter
once and for all
tomorrow
is there a problem
my mom won't let me walk that far on
weekdays can we do it on Saturday
well I really wanted tomorrow cause Bart
Levy would be hitting the gym then
Saturday is good I guess
and please don't bring Bartleby because
that would be cheating
Sonic what did he say what did your blue
Hedgehog ears learn
yeah don't leave us hanging out like
Uncle Chuck saggy balls in summer shorts
get training my only real friends were
going to war
Breaking News Bulletin everybody lock
your doors and find somewhere to hide
because World War III is officially upon
us and it is [__] [__] in fights are
breaking out all around America and all
the way to Japan
what is this about
well dumbass if you haven't been living
under a rock all week this is about
Sonic Underground versus the Sonic
Underground haters or what I'd rather
call them stupid [__] [__]
as a news anchor it's my job to give you
an unbiased opinion on this conflict but
frankly as a Sonic Underground fan I
don't give a [__]
now here's a word from the enemy
hey Yo's Onyx where you at tubby you do
realize it's going on 11 30 and I still
don't see you you are not [__] dead
as [__] are you if you are I'm going to
be really upset
foreign
don't let his words crawl under your
skin my love you will have your chance
at Revenge very soon I promise
first we have to clear out these
terrorists blocking our path pick up a
gun and fight
what are you waiting for a slap on the
ass get on the bus if you want to live
who the hell is that we didn't call for
backup
who gives a [__] he seems to be on our
side so let's do what he says
everyone fault don't you see who this is
this is none other than bus driver Bob
the manager of the [__] doodlebots we
can't know for sure that he won't turn
us over to the new boys
I wouldn't it's true I used to work with
them but I was fired when they disbanded
now I'm just a gay prostitute who stands
on the roadside in a pink Speedo
look if you don't want to trust me then
that's on you but I'm getting my sugary
sweet nipples out of here
before this neighborhood turns even more
into a wasteland of blood and poop
everyone hop on board we got a ride
wait a minute Bob take off your pants
what
that way you won't try any funny
business since your steamy moist booty
ho will have easy access to be bounded
like it's a meatloaf
so are you dropping boys I'd take you to
the local homeless shelter but it was
just nuked because a modern Sonic fan
was spotted there
take us straight to the Big Lots and
hurry Big Lots are you insane that's the
center of the chaos
yet I know
oh Deezer Barnaby we were just on our
way to the battlefield as well surely
you wouldn't mind giving us a ride
actually we're kind of full in here
oh haha that's fine then we can just
walk it's gonna be fun fighting
alongside one another
I mean you can try and squeeze on it if
you want I'm just saying that I don't
think there's enough room
no no it's fine I can tell when we are
not wanted
listen that's not what we're trying to
say at all
you know I spent three days putting this
deck together
also that I could be prepared for war
one that you guys started
perhaps you would like me to carry your
balls too I'm sure they're awfully heavy
why would you look at that the light
turned green
yeah maybe you should just go
Master Robert the Sonic Underground have
arrived on schedule
shall we commence with the attack
today
look they have light over there with
them and he's still breathing
that's not all there is look who else is
there with them
who's that is that Johnny Depp
are you dense woman that's not Johnny
Depp that's Robert you know the guy who
was going to be on the trillion dollar
bill
made exclusively by and for Bartleby
Montclair of the Dresden Clan
art Levy I'm scared what is a man you
hire doing with the Enemy and was it he
killed when he got trapped like a [__]
in a falling elevator
it would appear we are being haunted by
the sins of our past my little circus
peanut that is because he is not dead
and he never was
for you see Robert as well as I was
kidnapped by an evil man called
Professor major chord around a year ago
I escaped with the Echidna magic that
flows through my nuts
Robert was left behind but why he is on
their side now I do not know
foreign
foreign I forgot
robot before I rip your head clean up
your buddy tell me why you became evil
foreign
against me in that case let my friends
go for they have not wronged you in the
slightest bit
hey yeah that's a good point if you
don't hate Sonic Underground then you
shouldn't be in this club to begin with
from now on I'm the leader
well maybe I want to be the leader
oh hell no to Rooney doodle does not
take orders from a pumpkin
we configuration
yeah
the kings of Narnia Sonic you okay this
guy's not giving you any trouble as he
Narnia and all of its friends will never
forgive you for this
I told you we should have asked Barraco
for a ride now we're late for the fight
what if Sonic got raped
yeah well he didn't now get into a
battle pose so I can whip out your spell
book so after we win I can whip out my
big me 17 inch dick and smack it in the
faces of modern Sonic fans
are you sure you should bring your baby
brother into the battle World War III
might be a little dangerous for a
two-year-old
it's okay babies loved Sonic Underground
just as much as grown men Owen will need
a break every five minutes two changed
his diaper
you go and do that then [__] we'll
protect you and your baby brother at all
cost as well as Sonic Underground look
bro it's the Mighty Morphin Power
Rangers
they've come to help us [__] that look
out there on the skyscraper oh my gosh
is that the one and only Michael Mobius
no [__] that's just Jared Leto
so your manic I recognize you because
you're the cool one with Spanky hair
it's an honor to become your [__] for
today
those guys over there actually think
they can destroy Sonic Underground they
must have been born [__]
I bet when they poop they miss the
toilet and the ship splatters all over
the floor ha ha ha
um hello who invited you to the party
get lost loser you look like Harry
Potter with the PlayStation 4 on your
head
oh don't lay me Mr doodle pop is that
the way to treat an ally I even brought
you an army
an army
of course surely you didn't expect to
take them all on with just the four men
soldiers get down from the pickup truck
and come over here
this is Todd he's the leader of my
special forces
each of my children have been trained in
distinct forms of CQC secretly fighting
in wars that even the United States
government wasn't aware of you're not
going to find better soldiers of this
caliber Even If you hired suicide
bombers from Iraq
[__] I think we may be outnumbered on
this one maybe we should pack up and go
home Charles we should be back in time
to make your favorite grilled cheese for
dinner
only getting started
[Music]
the vocal lawyers are here from Japan
you heard about what's going on too
that's right why else do you think Anna
may always rips It Off
check it sibs it's the hillbilly farmer
and Muslim kid that we're barely
acquainted with
sup dudes glad to see you're still
kicking
we're also here in case anyone gives a
[__]
I don't believe this they really don't
give a [__]
and them too it's the rest of our fellow
acquaintances in which we barely know
Dr Robotnik why are you here have you
come just to see me get my ass shredded
if you mean that in a sexual way yes if
not no
because Sonic I will be the one to kill
you
so you better not lose to those guys you
hear me we're Rivals even when we're on
the same side just like Sora and we cool
when they join together to defeat zemnas
during Kingdom Hearts too except up like
Riku whose buff and saw is a twink you
and me are just fat guys
thanks for letting me spend the night at
Neverland Ranch until the war starts Mr
Jackson
if anything I should be the one thanking
you a heat of yours makes you look like
a pink marshmallow I just want to take a
bite how about after this war is over
you come live with me at Neverland Ranch
forever
okay but I'll have to tell my parents
first
I changed my mind
hey pink kid you shouldn't be here run
on home where it's safe let's go to
Neverland Ranch [__]
the hair that badass deflect don't give
a [__] attitude
wait you know me
sure my friend the man of my life and
holder of my heart said the Science Kid
he was researching you guys before
before he
listen Gerald we're sorry for your loss
but you must understand it's not safe
here be a big boy and go home and
protect your parents
I can't because fighting is what Sid
would have done the day that he died I
was scared and hit like a [__]
if I was strong to run that day said the
Science Kid might not have died and evil
would not reign as it does now oh you
have connections with Sid the Science
Kid I should have noticed because your
skin is freakishly pink and you have an
Orange Bowl for a nose
nevertheless my bitch's brother is right
A Beautiful World is achievable but only
if modern Sonic fans die
now are you going to stand there crying
like a mental irritated person or are
you going to grow a pair of fat balls
and fight like all life depended on I'm
in going to fight
very wise
we may come from different worlds we may
live different lives but one thing is
clear we are all Sonic Underground
sucking [__] am I wrong no I don't
think I am so stand side by side it
doesn't matter if you're a man or woman
blue or yellow racist or not racist we
are all Sonic Underground Warriors
[Music]
hey Captain Robert I'm getting bored and
we are almost out of tatino's pizza
bites can we start killing them now
community
oh okay
my comorbius Lookout there's a bullet
coming right for you
well at least it wasn't as Sonic
Underground character
it's a Sonic Underground and Club just
killed this fat baby are we just going
to stand around and let them get away
with it no oh
I think we should kill them don't you
[Applause]
[Music]
know
one of the main agents of the anti-sonic
underground members is coming right for
us
Tommy Oliver concentrate all of your
fire on him don't let him get near me or
my Spellbook
[Music]
don't you think I would have used it by
now wait maybe I do
quick are the ready metal objects around
us
there's a Russian plane flying up above
I think it's going to drop a nuke or
some
good imatic that's exactly what we need
to end this battle
I unleash the power of Zach's third
spell
sick hair door
huh is that all you've got that was
barely even a tickle
I'm going to feel more than that when I
bust my balls in your mouth
think again Robbie Rotten because you've
been hit by secure door your body is now
no different than that of a refrigerator
magnet
take them take more of my man motto's
thunderballs in your face
[Music]
I don't care if I'm white I'm going to
say it
this is the power of a Sonic Underground
you don't know
let's do this
[Music]
so your game is Michael too it's an
honor to fight alongside the King of Pop
why thank you I heard your name was also
Michael
it really is a small world which is good
because I like them small
you know if you were 12
I would have taken you the Neverland
Ranch
you know you're right at the perfect age
to squeeze in and become one of my
precious child soldiers what do you say
how about we unite together and
overthrow both the Sonic Underground and
the anti-fan club
laughs
damn it it's the freedom fighters from
the hit TV cart in Sonic Underground I
have to get away now
surround him boys show him what happens
to bullies who didn't have the fortune
of growing up watching Sonic Underground
what is this why are you all pulling
down your pants and pointing your stanky
butthole in my direction
by all means major chord if you're
scared then try to run
we welcome the challenge
[Music]
I don't get it they're just farting in
my face one after the next in quick
succession they're doing little damage
to me and yet somehow I can't find room
for escape how do I break free
simply put you don't no one escapes from
that legendary technique the freedom
fighter burning Rush
it's an endless cycle where they Corner
your ass from all sides
think of it like Itachi uchihas infinite
tsukiomi from Naruto although instead of
being caught in an illusion you're
trapped in real life while they beat you
up and fill your lungs with their rancid
gas until you pass out
I have to get out of here
[Music]
foreign
why don't you try it our way for once
after all we did just see you throw away
some Del Taco packages a second ago
look Pharaoh the battle is nearly
finished and the Sonic Underground
appear to be winning too should we just
head back home to Domino City since they
have things under control
no Kaiba Sonic the Hedgehog came to us
specifically two ate him in this war and
that's exactly what we're going to do
Now call upon your blue eyes white
dragon and fight
Pharaoh get back there's a grenade
coming our way
behind me Kaiba I played the magic card
salts to be feeling like now that we're
not must wait some turns before it
explodes and kills us
monsters is useless here pull out the
pistol I gave you
dual monsters
useless
you make me laugh watch this
you over there it's time to duel
okay then maybe later
you over yeah you the one who got his
legs blown off
would you like to battle in a game of
duel monsters
I don't get it why doesn't anybody want
to play a card game with e they're so
fun
about time you showed up all according
to plan
like you got me why did you send Sonic
the Hedgehog to me
why did you choose me to participate in
this war of Destiny knowing I was bad
cause Yuki that's exactly why you are
weak worthless just like dual monsters
I knew that no one would see you as a
threat so much so that you could walk
right through the battlefield and free
me with relativities
hold it right there do you really expect
me to let you walk away after all these
years I spent tracking you down
yep
so I was right L you decide to show your
face to me at last
do you know what this means don't you
I'm free I'm free and did nothing wrong
unlike you
you kidnapped me now I have all the
proof I need to turn you over to the
police
you started World War III and even worse
you hate Sonic Underground a man like
you will be executed for such crimes I
guess we can call this Checkmate [__]
who said I hit Sonic Underground oh so
you don't then say it say how much you
love it I love it I love Sonic
Underground so [__] much I can't
stand it
in that case then what are you after
what you really want
[Music]
ah
foreign
the leader of the anti-sonic underground
fan club has been defeated I hereby
declare a victory to be ours
I wouldn't put that sword away just yet
if I were you
good with the new boys as well
that is right Bartleby
they promised to pay me in frozen
burritos if I aided them in their
Conquest
I have been biding my time waiting since
10 minutes ago from across the street
from Big Lots at Kmart well you need to
stop it
no I don't think I will
now that you are all weakened from War I
can destroy you all rather easily then
we can have a new world where modern
Sonic fans can live freely and people
will be judged not for their tastes in
Sonic the Hedgehog but the size of their
hearts
that sounds like the crazy talk of the
madman
perhaps I am but you have to be a little
bit crazy like Jared Leto's Joker if you
plan to change the world
you better stop it
why don't you come up here and make me
tingai shinsee
[Music]
well it was fun while it lasted but me
and Edmond have to get our booties back
to Narnia
do you think you can hack that meteor to
slow us down long enough for us to
deduce a plan
sure to be
just use my hacking ability which I used
to add with sheets and had the massive
Rock bigger than my [__] ass that is
something that is definitely possible
okay then do it
[__] I am leading the media to you let
me take care of the caster
wait don't leave us
shut up
foreign
[Music]
it's too bad for you the time [__]
Nutley BBH
so the susano is as weak as wet toilet
paper compared to these muscles
you may have won this battle Bartleby
but victory in this war is still mine
now that the Sun is setting and so is
the meteor in this Big Lots parking lot
there's nothing left you can do to save
your pathetic friends
[Music]
follow
huh
my what a glorious little piece of
artonic fan art but who could have drawn
such a thing it's simply Too Perfect
well I'll be of course it is him
you sure took your time didn't you my
best friend
everybody look it's the one and only
timers one two three four five he's come
to rescue us in our most desperate hour
me my weakness but I don't know why
it's hard to serve
cause every time we saw about that
[__] I would have show up sooner but
you know how it is so what do you need
me to do beat some mom and sock fans
[__] asses no sweat I do that every
[__] day up in this piece of ass
it's terrible
there's a meteor that's going to kill us
all if you don't help us stop it Sonic
Underground may be destroyed forever
shut up [__] a woman hey you Sonic
what's going on here
there's a meteor that's going to kill us
all if you don't help us stop it Sonic
Underground could be destroyed forever
that's all perfect I was itching to
finally get a chance to use this
that sword is blue just like my bro
that's right the counterpart to the ba
that's right the counterpile to Bobby's
gold sort of Dresden the legendary blue
sword of the blue blood
in that case it would be a shame to have
one without the other you tame is 12
325 catch
[Music]
what's he going to do with two swords at
once
is going to combinated
itself
it's so manly that I accept it even if
it's kind of gay
[Music]
[Applause]
you did it Tamers you saved us now we
can all but this fighting behind us
no Sonic we did it
all right
you know even if you didn't show up I
was gonna destroy it myself anyway
and so with the Battle of one done the
Sonic are warriors return to the
Homeland as Heroes
[Music]
I may not Inspire
love it
[Music]
but what I can do is be here for you
to be here for you through the night
[Music]
I may not get mentioned
a magazine
[Music]
I may not inspire
Millions
[Music]
what I can do
is be here for you
here to you
tonight
[Music]
because the night is long and lonely
and make you cry
cry cry
[Music]
that's exactly why you are weak
worthless just like duel monsters
[Music]
give to you tonight
what I will do
[Music]
I still hear your voice when you sleep
next to me I still feel your touch in my
dreams
[Music]
but I don't know why without you it's
hard to
survive cause Every Time We Touch I get
this feeling and every time we kiss
[Music]
and every time
foreign
[Music]
your arms are my castle your heart is
you make me right
[Music]